(Bernadette:)It's the cutest thing.
(Bernadette:)Every time I have
dinner with his mom,
the next day I get jewelry.
(Amy:)Did you know that the iconic
Valentine's heart shape
(Amy:)is not actually based
on the shape of a human heart,
(Amy:)but rather on the shape
of the buttocks
(Amy:)of a female bending over?
(Penny:)Oh, so I spent seventh grade
(Penny:)dotting my I's
with little asses?
(Penny:)Cool.
(Zack:)Hey, Penny, how's it going?
(Penny:)Hey, Zack,
what are you doing here?
(Zack:)My dad's company prints
the menus for this place.
(Zack:)I'm just dropping off
some new ones laminated.
(Zack:)Makes 'em easier to clean
if people throw up on 'em.
(Zack:)Guess how I got the idea?
(Penny:)Yeah, I got it, I got it.
(Penny:)Uh, Zack, these are
my friends Bernadette and Amy.
(Bernadette:)- Hi.
- Hey.
(Amy:)Hoo.
(Zack:)Okay, well, it was
good to see you.
(Penny:)Yeah, you, too.
(Bernadette:)He's really cute.
How do you know him?
(Penny:)Oh, we went out
a couple of times.
(Amy:)I'm often flummoxed
by current slang.
Does "went out" mean
"had intercourse"?